Hi, I'm Dr. Kyle Bonesteel.
I'm the CEO of NeuroHealth Associates and NeuroStratus Inc., and I have spent my entire
career at the intersection of neuropsychology, diagnostics, and AI-driven healthcare innovation.
And I've had the opportunity to see a lot of different approaches to AI implementation.
And I've got to tell you, what has really, really impressed me about SYRV AI and Jarrod's
entire team is that they don't just understand the technology.
They understand how to actually make it work in real-world healthcare environments, appreciating
the importance of workflow integration and security and compliance and all the operational
realities that can make or break a successful implementation.
The other characteristic that has really stood out to me is the velocity and the speed
by which they work.
They're very responsive as a team.
I've worked with companies in the past that seem to get stuck in endless meetings and theoretical
discussions.
SYRV AI moves very, very differently.
They're action oriented, they communicate well, and they actually get stuff done and built.
And Jarrod and his team are also really amazing from a creativity standpoint.
I would have an idea for my software platform and sort of magically that idea would be
transformed into a tangible component within the platform.
They're able to move from concept to implementation in weeks rather than months, while still
having the extraordinary attention to detail that a project needs.
So I can't say enough good things about SYRV.
They've really taken our organization truly to the next level.
And I am super excited to see what the future holds for us thanks to SYRV.